(Leonard:)Okay. Well, once again,
you guys have a good...
(Leonard:)...whatever this is.
(Ramona:)Dr. Cooper, I have to tell you,
your friends are holding you back.
(Sheldon:)I prefer to think of it as
I'm pulling them forward.
(Ramona:)Halo night?
(Ramona:)A man with your intellectual gifts
doesn't waste an evening...
(Ramona:)...playing video games.
(Sheldon:)He does on Wednesdays.
(Ramona:)Not if he wants a Nobel Prize.
(Sheldon:)He does want that.
(Sheldon:)Does a man with my intellectual gifts
play paintball on weekends?
- What do you think?
- Drat.
- Now, shall we get back to work?
- I suppose.
(Sheldon:)Battlestar Galactica comes on tonight.
(Sheldon:)I guess I can wait for the DVD.
(Sheldon:)And then never, ever watch it.